<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.ksystemlog</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">سجلّات نظامك</name>
  <name xml:lang="az">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">kSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Ksystemlog</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">K Sistem Günlüğü</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KSystemLog</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKSystemLogxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KSystemLog 系统日志</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">KSystemLog</name>
  <summary>system log viewer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">عارض سجلّات النّظام</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="az">sistem jurnalı göstəricisi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Visor dels registres del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Visor dels registres del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Prohlížeč záznamů systému</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Systemprotokoll-Betrachter</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">προβολέας καταγραφών συστήματος</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">system log viewer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Visor del registro del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Süsteemi loginäitaja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Sistemaren egunkari erakuslea</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Järjestelmälokikatselin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">afficheur de journaux système</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">visor dos rexistros do sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Rendszernapló-megjelenítő</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">visor de registro de systema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">penampil catatan log sistem</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Visore dei registri di sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">시스템 로그 뷰어</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Systeemlogviewer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Systemloggvisar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Przeglądarka dziennika systemowego</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">visualizador de registos do sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Visualizador do registros do sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">vizualizor jurnale de sistem</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Просмотр системных журналов</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">prehliadač záznamov systému</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">vpogledovalnik v sistemski dnevnik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Visningsverktyg för systemloggar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">sistem günlüğü görüntüleyici</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Переглядач системних журналів</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxsystem log viewerxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">系统日志查看器</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">系統日誌檢視器</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KSystemLog show all logs of your system, grouped by General (Default system
    log, Authentication, Kernel, X.org...), and optional Services (Apache, Cups,
    etc, ...). It includes many features to read nicely your log files:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يعرض سجلات نظامك جميع سجلات المتعلقة بالحاسوب ، مجمعة بشكل عام (سجل النظام الافتراضي، المصادقة، النواة، أكس.أورغ ...) والخدمات الاختيارية (Apache ،Cups، إلخ ...). يتضمن العديد من الميزات لقراءة ملفات السجل الخاصة بك بشكل جيد:</p>
    <p xml:lang="az">KsystemLog, sisteminizin bütün jurnalını ümumi qruplaşdırılmış (Standart sistem jurnalı, Kimlik doğrulaması, Nüvə bidirişləri jurnalı, X.org jurnalı...) və əlavə xidmətlər (Apache, Cups və s...) şəklində baxmağa imkan verir. Bu tətbiq, jurnal faylları ilə sadə şəkildə işləmək aşağıdakı funksiyaları təqdim edir:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KSystemLog mostra tots els registres del sistema, agrupats per serveis generals (Registre predeterminat del sistema, Autenticació, Nucli, X.org...), i opcionals (Apache, CUPS...). Inclou moltes funcionalitats per a llegir de manera agradable els fitxers de registre:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">KSystemLog mostra tots els registres del sistema, agrupats per serveis generals (Registre predeterminat del sistema, Autenticació, Nucli, X.org...), i opcionals (Apache, CUPS...). Inclou moltes funcionalitats per a llegir de manera agradable els fitxers de registre:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KSystemLog zeigt alle Protokolle Ihres Systems in verschiedenen Gruppen wie Allgemein (Standard-Systemprotokoll, Authentifizierung, Kernel, X.org....) und optionale Dienste (Apache, Cups ...), usw.). Es enthält viele Funktionen, um Ihre Protokolldateien gut zu lesen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το KSystemLog εμφανίζει όλες τις καταγραφές του συστήματός σας, ομαδοποιημένες με βάση Γενικές (Προκαθορισμένες καταγραφές συστήματος, ταυτοποίηση, πυρήνας, X.org...) και προαιρετικές υπηρεσίες (Apache, Cups, κλπ, ...). Περιλαμβάνει πολλές λειτουργίες για να διαβάζετε με την ησυχία σας τα αρχεία καταγραφών σας:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KSystemLog show all logs of your system, grouped by General (Default system log, Authentication, Kernel, X.org...), and optional Services (Apache, Cups, etc, ...). It includes many features to read nicely your log files:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KSystemLog muestra todos los registros del sistema, agrupados por servicios generales (registro predeterminado del sistema, autenticación, kernel, X.org...) y opcionales (Apache, Cups...). Incluye diversas funcionalidades para leer los archivos de registro de forma agradable:</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KSystemLog näitab kõiki süsteemi logisid rühmitatuna üld- (vaikimisi süsteemilogi, autentimise, kerneli, X.org'i jne logid) ja lisateenuste (Apache, Cups jne) kaupa. Rakendus pakub mitmeid võimalusi logifaile kenasti ja arusaadavalt esitada:</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">KSystemLog-ek zure sistemako egunkari guztiak erakusten ditu, zerbitzu orokor (sistemaren egunkari lehenetsia, autentifikazioa, nukleoa, X-org, ...) eta aukerakoetan (Apache, Cups, etab., ...) taldekatuak. Eginbide ugari ditu zure egunkari fitxategiak irakurtzea behar bezala egiteko:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KSystemLog näyttää kaikki järjestelmälokit yleisiin (oletusloki, tunnistauminen, ydin, X.org…) ja lisäpalveluihin (Apache, Cups jne.) ryhmiteltynä. Sillä on monia ominaisuuksia, jotka helpottavat lokien tarkastelua:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KSystemLog affiche tous les journaux de votre système, groupés par catégories : Général (journal système par défaut, authentification, noyau, X.org, etc.) et services optionnels (Apache, Cups, etc.). Il inclut de nombreuses fonctionnalités facilitant la lecture de vos fichiers de journaux :</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KSystemLog mostra todos os rexistros do sistema, agrupados en xerais (rexistro predeterminado do sistema, autenticación, kernel, X.org…) e servizos opcionais (Apache, Cups, etc.). Inclúe moitas funcionalidades para ler facilmente os ficheiros de rexistro:</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A KSystemLog megjeleníti a rendszer összes naplófájlját, általános (alapértelmezett rendszernapló, hitelesítés, kernel, X.org…) és opcionális szolgáltatások (Apache, Cups, stb, …) szerint csoportosítva. Számos funkcióval segíti a naplófájlok olvasását:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">KSystemLog monstra omne registros de tu systema, gruppate per Registro General  (registro de systema redefinite, Authentication, Kernel, X.org...) e Servitios optional  (Apache, Cups, etc, ...). Illo  include multe characteristicas per leger agradibilemente tu files de registro:</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">KSystemLog menampilkan semua catatan log sistemmu, dikelompokkan berdasarkan General (Catatan log sistem baku, Autentikasi, Kernel, X.org...), dan Layanan (Apache, Cups, dll, ...) opsional. Serta banyak fitur-fitur pembacaan secara baik file-file catatan log-mu:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KSystemLog mostra tutti i registri di sistema, raggruppati per Generale (registro predefinito di sistema, autenticazione, Kernel, X.org...) e Servizi opzionali (Apache, Cups, ecc, ...). Include molte funzionalità per leggere bene i file di registro:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KSystemLog는 시스템의 모든 로그를 볼 수 있는 도구입니다. 일반(기본 시스템 로그, 인증, 커널, X.org, ...) 및 추가 서비스(Apache, CUPS, ...) 로그로 분류합니다. 로그 파일을 읽기 편하게 하는 도구를 제공합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KSystemLog toont alle logs op uw systeem, gegroepeerd op Algemeen (Standaard systeemlog, Authenticatie, Kernel, X.org...) en optionele services (Apache, Cups, etc, ...). Het bevat vele mogelijkheden om uw logbestanden netjes te lezen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">KSystemLog viser alle loggane på systemet, gruppert etter generelle loggar (standard systemloggar, autentisering, kjernen, X.org, …) og tenesteloggar (Apache, Cups, …). Programmet har mange funksjonar for lettare lesing av loggfilene:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KSystemLog pokazuje wszystkie dzienniki systemu, zgrupowane wg ogólnych (domyślny dziennik systemu, uwierzytelnienie, jądro, X.org...), oraz opcjonalnych usług (Apache, Cups, itp.). Zawiera wiele ułatwień do czytania plików dziennika:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KSystemLog mostra todos os registos do seu sistema, agrupados por Geral (Registo predefinido do sistema, Autenticação, 'Kernel', X.org...), e pelos Serviços opcionais (Apache, Cups, etc, ...). Inclui muitas funcionalidades agradáveis para ler os seus ficheiros de registo de forma agradável:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KSystemLog mostra todos os registros do seu sistema, agrupados por Geral (Registro padrão do sistema, Autenticação, Kernel, X.org...), e por Serviços opcionais (Apache, Cups, etc, ...). Inclui muitas funcionalidades agradáveis para leitura dos arquivos de registro:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">KSystemLog — приложение для просмотра системных журналов. Приложение позволяет просматривать основные (системный журнал по умолчанию, журнал аутентификации, журнал сообщений ядра, журнал X.org) и дополнительные журналы (Apache, CUPS и других). Приложение использует следующие функции для упрощения работы с файлами журналов:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KSystemLog zobrazí všetky záznamy vášho systému, zoskupené podľa všeobecných (predvolený systémový záznam, autentifikácia, jadro, X.org...) a voliteľných služieb (Apache, Cups, atď...) Zahŕňa veľa funkcií na pekné čítanie vašich súborov záznamov:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KSystemLog prikaže vse dnevnike vašega sistema, razvrščene v skupine Splošno (Privzeti sistemski dnevnik, overjanje, Kernel, X.org ...) in izbirne storitve (Apache, Cups itd.). Vsebuje veliko funkcij za lažje branje datotek dnevnika:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Ksystemlog visar alla loggar i systemet, grupperade enligt allmänna (standardsystemlogg, behörighetskontroll, kärna, X.org, ...) och valfria tjänster (Apache, Cups, etc.). Det inkluderar många funktioner för att snyggt läsa loggfiler:</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">K Sistem Günlüğü, sisteminizin tüm günlüklerini gösterir. Günlükler Genel (öntanımlı sistem günlüğü, kimlik doğrulama, çekirdek, X.org vb.) ve isteğe bağlı hizmetler (Apache, Cups vb.) olarak gruplanır. Günlük dosyalarınızı rahatça okuyabilmeniz için birçok özellik içerir:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KSystemLog може показувати усі журнали роботи вашої системи. Журнали поділено на загальні (типовий журнал системи, журнал розпізнавання, журнал ядра, журнал X.org...) та додаткові журнали служб (Apache, CUPS тощо). Передбачено багато можливостей для зручного перегляду журналів:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKSystemLog show all logs of your system, grouped by General (Default system log, Authentication, Kernel, X.org...), and optional Services (Apache, Cups, etc, ...). It includes many features to read nicely your log files:xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">KSystemLog 能够显示系统的所有日志，并可按照常规 (默认系统日志、身份验证、内核、X.org...)和额外服务 (Apache、Cups 等) 进行分组。它的界面功能强大，让您可以方便清晰地阅读日志文件：</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">KSystemLog 顯示您系統的所有日誌，並分類成「一般」（預設系統日誌、認證、內核及 X.org 等…），和選用服務（Apache、Cups 等等…）。其包含許多能讓您更好閱讀日誌檔案的功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Colorize log lines depending on their severities</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">تلوين خطوط السجل حسب خطورتها</li>
      <li xml:lang="az">Üstünlüyündən asılı olaraq jurnal sətirlərinin rənglənməsi</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Acoloreix les línies de registre en funció de la seva severitat</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Acolorix les línies de registre en funció de la seua gravetat</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Farbige Anzeige der Protokollzeilen abhängig von der Protokollstufe</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Ο χρωματισμός γραμμών καταγραφών εξαρτάται από τη σπουδαιότητά τους</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Colourise log lines depending on their severities</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Líneas de registro coloreadas según su severidad</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Logiridade eristamine värviga vastavalt raskusastmele</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Koloreztatu egunkari lerroak bere larritasunaren arabera</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">lokirivien väritys niiden vakavuusasteen mukaan</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Mise en couleur des lignes des journaux en fonction de leur sévérité</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Colorar as liñas de rexistro segundo a súa gravidade</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Sorok színezése a fontosságuk szerint</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Colora lineas de registro dependente de lor severitate</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Pewarnaan baris log tergantung pada kepelikannya</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Colorazione delle righe del registro in base alla loro gravità</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">심각도에 따라서 로그 줄 자동 색상 지정</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Logregels kleuren afhankelijk van hun ernst</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Fargelegg logglinjer basert på alvorsgrad</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Zabarwianie wierszy dziennika w zależności od ich znaczenia</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Colorir as linhas de registo de acordo com a sua criticidade</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Colorir as linhas de registro de acordo com a sua criticidade</li>
      <li xml:lang="ro">Colorează liniile de jurnal conform severității acestora</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Использование выделения цветом для событий различного приоритета;</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Zafarbiť riadky záznamu podľa ich závažnosti</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Pobarvaj vrstice dnevnika v odvisnosti od resnosti</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Färglägg loggrader beroende på deras svårighetsgrad</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Günlük dosyalarını önceliklerine göre renklendir</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Розфарбовування записів журналу за їхньою критичністю</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxColorize log lines depending on their severitiesxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">根据严重程度将日志信息行显示为不同颜色</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">基於日誌中行的重要性上色</li>
      <li>Tabbed view to allow displaying several logs at the same time</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">عرض مبوب للسماح بعرض عدة سجلات في نفس الوقت</li>
      <li xml:lang="az">Bir neçə jurnalın eyni vaxtda vərəqlər şəkildində göstərilməsi</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Vista amb pestanyes que permet mostrar diversos registres a la vegada</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista amb pestanyes que permet mostrar diversos registres a la vegada</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Anzeige verschiedener Protokolldateien in einzelnen Unterfenstern.</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Προβολή σε καρτέλες που επιτρέπει την εμφάνιση πολλών καταγραφών ταυτόχρονα</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Tabbed view to allow displaying several logs at the same time</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Vista en pestañas para poder mostrar varios registros a la vez</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Kaartidega vaade, mis lubab näha korraga mitut logi</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Fitxadun ikuspegia aldi berean hainbat egunkari bistaratzeko</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">välilehtinäkymä useiden lokien samanaikaiseen tarkasteluun</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">La vue en onglets permet d'afficher plusieurs journaux en même temps</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Vista con lapelas que permite mostrar varios rexistros simultaneamente</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Lapokra osztott nézet több naplófájl egyszerre történő megjelenítéséhez</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Vista a schedas que permitte monstrar plure registros al mesme tempore</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Tampilan bertab untuk memungkinkan penayangan log di waktu yang sama</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Vista a schede, che permette la visualizzazione di più registri nello stesso tempo</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">여러 로그를 탭을 통해서 동시에 표시</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">In tabbladen tonen om verschillende logs tegelijk te tonen</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Fanebasert vising av fleire loggar samtidig</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Widok w kartach umożliwiający przeglądanie kilku dzienników jednocześnie</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Vista em páginas que permite mostrar vários registos ao mesmo tempo</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Exibição em abas que permite apresentar vários registros ao mesmo tempo</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Использование вкладок для одновременного просмотра нескольких журналов;</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Kartový pohľad na umožnenie zobrazenia niekoľkých záznamov naraz</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Pogled z zavihki, ki dovoljuje prikaz več dnevnikov istočasno</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Flikvy för att tillåta att flera loggar visas samtidigt</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Aynı anda birden çok günlüğü görüntüleyebilmek için sekmeli görünüm</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Перегляд з вкладками, який надає вам змогу бачити декілька журналів одразу</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxTabbed view to allow displaying several logs at the same timexx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">标签页视图，可同时显示多个日志</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">分頁檢視，允許同時顯示多個日誌</li>
      <li>Auto display new lines logged</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">عرض آلي للسطور المضافة في السجل</li>
      <li xml:lang="az">Yeni jurnal sətirlərinin avtomatik göstərilməsi</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Presentació automàtica de les línies noves del registre</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Presentació automàtica de les línies noves del registre</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Automatische Anzeiger neuer Protokollzeilen</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Αυτόματη εμφάνιση νέων γραμμών καταγραφής.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Auto display new lines logged</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Muestra de forma automática las nuevas líneas registradas</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Lisanduvate logikirjete automaatne näitamine</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Automatikoki bistaratu egunkarira gehitutako lerro berriak</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">uusien lokirivien näyttäminen automaattisesti</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Affichage automatique des nouvelles lignes des journaux</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Mostrar automaticamente as novas liñas rexistradas</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Új bejegyzések automatikus megjelenítése</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Monstra automaticamente nove lineas registrate</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Auto tayang baris baru yang di-log</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Visualizzazione automatica delle nuove righe registrate</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">새로 로그에 추가된 줄 자동 표시</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Automatische nieuwe logregels weergeven</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Automatisk vising av nye logglinjer</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wyświetlanie nowych wierszy, które trafiły do dziennika</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Mostrar automaticamente as novas linhas registadas</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Exibição automática das novas linhas registradas</li>
      <li xml:lang="ro">Afișează automat noile linii înregistrate</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Автоматический показ новых записей;</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Automaticky zobraziť nové zaznamenané riadky</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Avtomatski prikaz novih zabeleženih vrstic dnevnika</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Visa automatiskt nya loggade rader</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Yeni günlüklenen satırları kendiliğinden göster</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Автоматичний показ нових рядків журналу</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAuto display new lines loggedxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">自动显示新日志记录</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">自動顯示新記錄的行</li>
      <li>Detailed information for each log lines</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">معلومات مفصلة عن كل سطر من الأسطر</li>
      <li xml:lang="az">Hər jurnal sətri haqqında ətraflı məlumat</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Informació detallada per a cada línia de registre</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Informació detallada per a cada línia de registre</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Ausführliche Informationen zu jeder Protokoll-Zeile</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Λεπτομερής πληροφόρηση για κάθε γραμμή καταγραφής</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Detailed information for each log lines</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Información detallada para las líneas de cada registro</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Üksikasjalik teave iga logirea kohta</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Informazio xehatua egunkari lerro bakoitzeko</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">yksityiskohtaiset tiedot kustakin lokirivistä</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Informations détaillées pour chaque ligne des journaux</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Información detallada en cada liña de rexistro</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Részletes információk minden egyes sorhoz</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Informationdetaliate per cata lineas de registro (log)</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Informasi terperinci untuk setiap baris log</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Informazioni dettagliate per ciascuna riga del registro</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">각각 로그 줄별 자세한 정보</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Gedetailleerde informatie voor elke logregel</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Detaljert informasjon om kvar logglinje</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Szczegółowe dane dla każdego wiersza dziennika</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Informação detalhada para cada linha do registo</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Informação detalhada para cada linha do registro</li>
      <li xml:lang="ro">Informații detaliate pentru fiecare linie din jurnal</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Подробная информация о каждой строке журнала.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podrobné informácie pre každý riadok záznamu</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Podrobna informacija za vsako zabeleženo vrstico</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Detaljerad information för varje loggrad</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Her bir günlük satırı için ayrıntılı bilgi</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Докладна інформація щодо кожного рядка журналу</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDetailed information for each log linesxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">每行日志均可显示详情</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">詳細列出每行日誌的資訊</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=ksystemlog</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=ksystemlog</url>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.ksystemlog.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/ksystemlog/ksystemlog.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <binary>ksystemlog</binary>
  </provides>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <releases>
    <release version="22.04.3" date="2022-07-07"/>
    <release version="22.04.2" date="2022-06-09"/>
    <release version="22.04.1" date="2022-05-12"/>
    <release version="22.04.0" date="2022-04-21"/>
  </releases>
</component>
